{"data":[{"question":"Seven of planets rotate in the same direction as their orbital motions, while Venus and Uranus rotate in the opposite direction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"planets ","b":"as ","c":"while ","d":"opposite direction","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Of planets-> planets","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A good exercise program helps teach people to avoid the habits that might shorten the  lives.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"helps teach ","b":"to avoid ","c":"might ","d":"the  ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- The-> their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody should be able to find fault in that argument.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"should ","b":"fault ","c":"in ","d":"argument","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Fault in-> fault with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Since the early 1990's Luther Burbank bred a spineless variety of cactus that can be eaten as food.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Since ","b":"variety of ","c":"can be eaten ","d":"as food","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Since-> In","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A drama is a story intended to be presented by actors onto a stage.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A drama ","b":"intended to ","c":"presented ","d":"onto ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Onto-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The relationship between law to liberty is even more paradoxical than that between law and order.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"between ","b":"even ","c":"that ","d":"and ","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Between-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"An opera combines the excitement of drama and spectacle to the power of music.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"An ","b":"excitement ","c":"drama ","d":"to ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The Alexandria Gazette, published daily since 1797, is the oldest regularly published  newspapers  in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"published ","b":"oldest ","c":"newspapers                                      ","d":"in the ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Newspapers-> newspaper","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Unlike ordinary light sources, a laser sends out a narrow beam of light on only one direction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Unlike ","b":"sources","c":"sends out ","d":"on only ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- On only-> to only","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A thorough study of mythology requires familiarity for the properties of plants and trees, and the habits of wild birds and beasts.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"study ","b":"familiarity ","c":"habits ","d":"wild ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Familiarity-> the familiarity","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}